[
  {"question":"書き言葉はどれ？","correct":"しかし","choices":["しかし","でも","ちょっと","ねえ"]},
  {"question":"話し言葉はどれ？","correct":"だよね","choices":["だよね","しかしながら","ゆえに","また"]},
  {"question":"書き言葉はどれ？","correct":"及び","choices":["及び","それで","だから","やばい"]},
  {"question":"話し言葉はどれ？","correct":"かな","choices":["かな","しかし","故に","及び"]},
  {"question":"書き言葉はどれ？","correct":"なお","choices":["なお","ねぇ","もう","やっぱ"]},
  {"question":"話し言葉はどれ？","correct":"まじで","choices":["まじで","したがって","ゆえ","よって"]},
  {"question":"書き言葉はどれ？","correct":"従って","choices":["従って","だから","だって","ほんとに"]},
  {"question":"話し言葉はどれ？","correct":"やっぱり","choices":["やっぱり","それゆえ","および","したがって"]},
  {"question":"書き言葉はどれ？","correct":"つまり","choices":["つまり","てか","えっと","やばい"]},
  {"question":"話し言葉はどれ？","correct":"ほんと","choices":["ほんと","ゆえに","および","さらに"]},
  {"question":"書き言葉はどれ？","correct":"例えば","choices":["例えば","やばい","すごい","ねえ"]},
  {"question":"話し言葉はどれ？","correct":"じゃん","choices":["じゃん","しかしながら","及び","ゆえに"]},
  {"question":"書き言葉はどれ？","correct":"最も","choices":["最も","めっちゃ","かなり","すごい"]},
  {"question":"話し言葉はどれ？","correct":"ほんとに","choices":["ほんとに","従って","ゆえに","なお"]},
  {"question":"書き言葉はどれ？","correct":"したがって","choices":["したがって","だから","やっぱ","すごく"]},
  {"question":"話し言葉はどれ？","correct":"すごく","choices":["すごく","ゆえに","および","さらに"]},
  {"question":"書き言葉はどれ？","correct":"しかしながら","choices":["しかしながら","やばい","ね","ちょっと"]},
  {"question":"話し言葉はどれ？","correct":"ね","choices":["ね","しかし","ゆえに","及び"]},
  {"question":"書き言葉はどれ？","correct":"ちなみに","choices":["ちなみに","それでさ","ほんと","やっぱ"]},
  {"question":"話し言葉はどれ？","correct":"ちょっと","choices":["ちょっと","しかしながら","ゆえに","なお"]}
]
